Guide to the McKim Mead & White Architectural Records Collection circa 1875-1950 PR 42
© 2011 New-York Historical Society
- Series III: Specifications
  - Adelphi College- administration, recreation, and classroom buildings (Box III.1, Folder 2)
  - American Military Cemetery, Florence, Italy (Box III.1, Folder 3)
  - Amherst College (Box III.1, Folder 4)
  - Amherst College (Box III.1, Folder 5)
  - Amherst College (Box III.1, Folder 6)
  - Amherst College (Box III.2, Folder 1)
  - Amherst College, Chemistry Building (Box III.2, Folder 2)
  - Amherst College, Dormitories (Box III.2, Folder 3)
  - Amherst College, Faculty Housing, Merrill Place (Box III.2, Folder 4)
  - Amherst College, Gymnasium (Box III.2, Folder 5)
  - Amherst College, Infirmary (Box III.2, Folder 6)
  - Amherst College, Johnson Chapel (Box III.2, Folder 7)
  - Amherst College, Library (Box III.3, Folder 1)
  - Amherst College, Morgan Library (Box III.3, Folder 2)
  - Amherst College, Pratt Field Gates (Box III.3, Folder 3)
  - Amherst College, Natatorium (Box III.3, Folder 4)
  - Amherst College, Power House (Box III.3, Folder 5)
  - Amherst College, School House (Box III.3, Folder 6)
  - Amherst College, Service Building (Box III.3, Folder 7)
  - Amherst College, Squash Courts (Box III.3, Folder 8)
  - Amherst College, Theatre (Box III.3, Folder 9)
  - Arlington Memorial Bridge (Box III.3, Folder 10)
  - Arlington Memorial Bridge (Box III.3, Folder 11)
  - Arlington Memorial Bridge (Box III.4, Folder 1)
  - Arlington Memorial Bridge (Box III.4, Folder 2)
  - Arlington Memorial Bridge (Box III.4, Folder 3)
  - Arlington Memorial Bridge (Box III.4, Folder 4)
  - Arlington Memorial Bridge (Box III.4, Folder 5)
  - Bank of Buffalo (Box III.5, Folder 1)
  - Bank of Montreal (Box III.5, Folder 2)
  - Bank of Montreal (Box III.5, Folder 3)
  - Bank of Montreal (Box III.5, Folder 4)
  - Bank of Montreal (Box III.5, Folder 5)
  - Bank of Montreal, NY Branch (Box III.6, Folder 1)
  - Bank of Montreal, Winnipeg Branch (Box III.6, Folder 2)
  - Barnard College Dormitories, plumbing and heating (Box III.6, Folder 3)
  - Barnard College, Greenhouse and Headhouse (Box III.6, Folder 4)
  - Beard or Lorillard, Tuxedo Park, NY Residence (Box III.6, Folder 5)
  - Bellevue Hospital (Box III.7, Folder 1)
  - Bellevue Hospital (Box III.7, Folder 2)
  - Bellevue Hospital (Box III.7, Folder 3)
  - Bellevue Hospital (Box III.7, Folder 4)
  - Bellevue Hospital (Box III.7, Folder 5)
  - Bellevue Hospital (Box III.7, Folder 6)
  - Bellevue Hospital (Box III.7, Folder 7)
  - Bellevue Hospital, Boiler House and Coaling Station (Box III.8, Folder 1)
  - Bellevue Hospital, Garage (Box III.8, Folder 2)
  - Bellevue Hospital- hardware schedule, plumbing fixtures, and prints (Box III.8, Folder 3)
  - Bellevue Hospital, Laundry Building (Box III.8, Folder 4)
  - Bellevue Hospital, Nurses Training School (Box III.8, Folder 5)
  - Bellevue Hospital, Outpatient and Female Dormitories (Box III.8, Folder 6)
  - Bellevue Hospital, Pathological Department (Box III.9, Folder 1)
  - Bellevue Hospital, Pavilions (Box III.9, Folder 2)
  - Bellevue Hospital, Pavilions (Box III.9, Folder 3)
  - Bellevue Hospital, Pavilions (Box III.10, Folder 1)
  - Blair, E.T., Chicago, ILL (Box III.10, Folder 2)
  - Blakey Low, Mr. Carroll Residence, New Rochelle, NY (Box III.10, Folder 3)
  - Bloomingsdale, Lyman G., Mausoleum at Salem Fields Cemetery, NY (Box III.10, Folder 4)
  - Boston Public Library (Box III.10, Folder 5)
  - Boston Music Hall (Box III.10, Folder 6)
  - Bowdoin College, Entrance Gates and Walker Art Gallery, ME (Box III.10, Folder 7)
  - Bowdoin College, Swimming Pool, Brunswick, ME (Box III.10, Folder 8)
  - Bowdoin College Union, Brunswick, ME (Box III.10, Folder 9)
  - Bradford, Lyndsay- stable and cottage (Box III.11, Folder 1)
  - 60 Broadway (Box III.11, Folder 2)
  - 38-06 to 38-14 Broadway, Long Island City, NY (building or Wesleyan University, project never built) (Box III.11, Folder 3)
  - Bronx, Grit Chamber (Box III.11, Folder 4)
  - Brooklyn Botanical Gardens (Box III.11, Folder 5)
  - Brooklyn Botanical Gardens (Box III.11, Folder 6)
  - Brooklyn Botanical Gardens, Flatbush Avenue Gates (Box III.11, Folder 7)
  - Brooklyn Institute (Box III.11, Folder 8)
  - Brooklyn Institute (Box III.12, Folder 1)
  - Brooklyn Institute (Box III.12, Folder 2)
  - Brooklyn Institute, Duplicates (Box III.12, Folder 3)
  - Brooks, Phillips- Monument (Box III.12, Folder 4)
  - Burke Foundations, White Plains, NY (Box III.13, Folder 1)
  - Burlington City Hall, Burlington, VT (Box III.13, Folder 2)
  - Butler Art Gallery, Youngstown, Ohio (Box III.13, Folder 3)
  - Butler Art Gallery, Youngstown, Ohio (Box III.14, Folder 1)
  - Butler Art Gallery, Youngstown, Ohio (Box III.14, Folder 2)
  - Century Club (Box III.14, Folder 3)
  - Church of the Ascension (Box III.14, Folder 4)
  - Columbia University, Avery Building (Box III.15, Folder 1)
  - Columbia University, Avery Building (Box III.15, Folder 2)
  - Columbia University, Business Building (Box III.15, Folder 3)
  - Columbia University, Casa Italiana (Box III.15, Folder 4)
  - Columbia University, Chemistry Building (Box III.15, Folder 5)
  - Columbia University, Chemistry Building (Box III.15, Folder 6)
  - Columbia University, Engineering Building (Box III.16, Folder 1)
  - Columbia University, Faculty Club, new pent house (Box III.16, Folder 2)
  - Columbia University, Faculty House (Box III.16, Folder 3)
  - Columbia University, Furnald Hall (Box III.16, Folder 4)
  - Columbia University, General (Box III.16, Folder 5)
  - Columbia University, General (Box III.16, Folder 6)
  - Columbia University, Granite step in connection with memorial close, class 1891 (Box III.17, Folder 1)
  - Columbia University, Hamilton Hall (Box III.17, Folder 2)
  - Columbia University, Hartley and Livingston Halls (Box III.17, Folder 3)
  - Columbia University, Journalism Building (Box III.17, Folder 4)
  - Columbia University, Kent Hall (Box III.17, Folder 5)
  - Columbia University, Kent Hall (Box III.17, Folder 6)
  - Columbia University, Library (Box III.17, Folder 7)
  - Columbia University, Library (Box III.18, Folder 1)
  - Columbia University, Library (Box III.18, Folder 2)
  - Columbia University, Natural Sciences, Schermerhorn Hall (Box III.18, Folder 3)
  - Columbia University, Natural Sciences, Schermerhorn Hall (Box III.18, Folder 4)
  - Columbia University, Natural Sciences, Schermerhorn Hall (Box III.18, Folder 5)
  - Columbia University, Pharmacy (Box III.18, Folder 6)
  - Columbia University, Philosophy (Box III.19, Folder 1)
  - Columbia University, Physics Building (Box III.19, Folder 2)
  - Columbia University, Physics Building (Box III.19, Folder 3)
  - Columbia University, President's House (Box III.19, Folder 4)
  - Columbia University, Students Hall (Box III.19, Folder 5)
  - Columbia University, Students Hall (Box III.20, Folder 1)
  - Columbia University, Temporary Laboratory Building (Box III.20, Folder 2)
  - Columbia University, University Hall (Box III.20, Folder 3)
  - Columbia University, University Hall (Box III.20, Folder 4)
  - Columbia University, University Hall (Box III.20, Folder 5)
  - Columbia University, Women's Residence Hall (Box III.20, Folder 6)
  - Colgate University, Administration Building (Box III.21, Folder 1)
  - Colgate University, East and West Halls (Box III.21, Folder 2)
  - Commercial National Bank, Shreveport, LA (Box III.21, Folder 3)
  - Commercial National Bank, Shreveport, LA (Box III.21, Folder 4)
  - Commercial National Bank, Shreveport, LA (Box III.21, Folder 5)
  - Commercial National Bank, Shreveport, LA (Box III.21, Folder 6)
  - Commercial National Bank, Shreveport, LA (Box III.21, Folder 7)
  - Cornell Medical College (Box III.22, Folder 1)
  - Cornell Medical College (Box III.22, Folder 2)
  - Cromwell, Frederic (Box III.22, Folder 3)
  - Cuban National Hotel, Havana, Cuba (Box III.22, Folder 4)
  - Cuban National Hotel, Havana, Cuba (Box III.22, Folder 5)
  - Cuban National Hotel, Havana, Cuba (Box III.22, Folder 6)
  - Detroit BI-Centennial Memorial, MI (Box III.23, Folder 1)
  - Downtown Building Company, NY (Box III.23, Folder 2)
  - Downtown Building Company, NY (Box III.23, Folder 3)
  - First Presbyterian Church, Chattanooga, TN- wood frames (Box III.23, Folder 4)
  - Fort Benning Infantry School (Box III.23, Folder 5)
  - Fort Benning Infantry School (Box III.23, Folder 6)
  - Fort Greene Park, NY (Box III.23, Folder 7)
  - Fountain for H.L. Higginson (Box II.23, Folder 8)
  - Gimbel Building, Subway passage, NY (Box III.24, Folder 1)
  - Girard Trust Company (Box III.24, Folder 2)
  - Girard Trust Company (Box III.24, Folder 3)
  - Girard Trust Company (Box III.24, Folder 4)
  - Girard Trust Company (Box III.24, Folder 5)
  - Girard Trust Company (Box III.24, Folder 6)
  - Girard Trust Company (Box III.24, Folder 7)
  - Girard Trust Company (Box III.25, Folder 1)
  - Girard Trust Company (Box III.25, Folder 2)
  - Girard Trust Company (Box III.25, Folder 3)
  - Girard Trust Company (Box III.25, Folder 4)
  - Girard Trust Company, Philadelphia, PA (Box III.25, Folder 5)
  - Governors Island Hospital, NY (Box III.25, Folder 6)
  - Governors Island, Hospital, NY (Box III.26, Folder 1)
  - Governors Island, Infantry Regimental Barracks (Box III.26, Folder 2)
  - Governors Island, NY Detachment Barracks (Box III.26, Folder 3)
  - Governors Island, Ventilation Building (Box Flat files, Folder FF91)
  - Hadley Falls Trust Company, Holyokes Mass (Box III.27, Folder 1)
  - Harlem Valley Hospital (Box III.27, Folder 2)
  - Harlem Valley Hospital (Box III.27, Folder 3)
  - Harlem Valley Hospital (Box III.27, Folder 4)
  - Harlem Valley Hospital (Box III.27, Folder 5)
  - Harlem Valley Hospital (Box III.28, Folder 1)
  - Harriman, Ripley. and Company, Air conditioning plant installation (Box III.28, Folder 2)
  - Harvard Club, Additions and alterations (Box III.28, Folder 3)
  - Harvard Club, Additions and alterations (Box III.29, Folder 1)
  - Harvard Club, Additions and alterations (Box III.29, Folder 2)
  - Harvard Club, Additions and alterations (Box III.29, Folder 3)
  - Harvard Club, Additions and alterations (Box III.29, Folder 4)
  - Harvard Club, Ladies Annex- building department papers (Box III.29, Folder 5)
  - Harvard University, School of Architecture (Box III.29, Folder 6)
  - Harvard University, School of Business Administration (Box III.30, Folder 1)
  - Harvard University, School of Business Administration (Box III.30, Folder 2)
  - Harvard University, School of Business Administration (Box III.30, Folder 3)
  - Hooker Electrochemical Company, NY Office and Tacoma, Washington (Box III.30, Folder 4)
  - Hotel Pennsylvania (Box III.30, Folder 5)
  - Hotel Pennsylvania (Box III.31, Folder 1)
  - Hotel Pennsylvania (Box III.31, Folder 2)
  - Hotel Pennsylvania (Box III.31, Folder 3)
  - Hotel Pennsylvania (Box III.31, Folder 4)
  - Hotel Pennsylvania (Box III.31, Folder 5)
  - Hotel Pennsylvania (Box III.32, Folder 1)
  - Hotel Pennsylvania (Box III.32, Folder 2)
  - Hotel Pennsylvania (Box III.32, Folder 3)
  - Hotel Pennsylvania (Box III.32, Folder 4)
  - Hotel Pennsylvania (Box III.32, Folder 5)
  - Kimball, Mrs. W.W.- monument (Box III.33, Folder 1)
  - Knickerbocker Trust Company, 34th Street, NY (Box III.33, Folder 2)
  - Knickerbocker Trust Company, 34th Street, NY (Box III.33, Folder 3)
  - Library Building, Smithtown, Long Island, NY (Box III.33, Folder 4)
  - Lincoln Alliance Bank (Box III.33, Folder 5)
  - Lincoln Monument, Chicago, ILL (Box III.33, Folder 6)
  - Lincoln Statue, London, England (Box III.33, Folder 7)
  - Man O' War Statue, Lexington, KY (Box III.33, Folder 8)
  - McCarren Park Shelter, Brooklyn, NY (Box III.33, Folder 9)
  - Metropolitan Club, NY (Box III.34, Folder 1)
  - Metropolitan Club, NY (Box III.34, Folder 2)
  - Metropolitan Club, NY (Box III.34, Folder 3)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, NY (Box III.34, Folder 4)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, NY (Box III.34, Folder 5)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, Addition "E" (Box III.34, Folder 6)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, Addition "G" (Box III.35, Folder 1)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, Addition "H" (Box III.35, Folder 2)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, Addition "J" (Box III.35, Folder 3)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, Addition "K" (Box III.35, Folder 4)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, Carpenter Shop (Box III.35, Folder 5)
  - Middlebury College, Field House (Box III.35, Folder 6)
  - Middlesex Hospital, Connecticut (Box III.35, Folder 7)
  - Middlesex Hospital, Connecticut (Box III.36, Folder 1)
  - Minneapolis Museum of Fine Arts, Minnesota (Box III.36, Folder 2)
  - Morgan, J.P. Library, NY (Box III.36, Folder 3)
  - Municipal Building, NY (Box III.36, Folder 4)
  - Municipal Building, NY (Box III.36, Folder 5)
  - Municipal Building, NY (Box III.36, Folder 6)
  - Municipal Building, NY (Box III.37, Folder 1)
  - Municipal Building, NY (Box III.37, Folder 2)
  - Municipal Building, NY (Box III.37, Folder 3)
  - Municipal Building, NY (Box III.37, Folder 4)
  - Municipal Building, NY (Box III.37, Folder 5)
  - Municipal Building, NY (Box III.37, Folder 6)
  - Municipal Building, NY (Box III.37, Folder 7)
  - National City Annex, 13 East 42nd Street, NY (Box III.38, Folder 1)
  - National City Bank, Park Avenue 57th Street, NY (Box III.38, Folder 2)
  - National City Bank, Fifth Avenue, NY (Box III.38, Folder 3)
  - National City Bank, 52 Wall Street (Box III.38, Folder 4)
  - National City Bank, 52 Wall Street (Box III.38, Folder 5)
  - National City Bank, 52 Wall Street (Box III.39, Folder 1)
  - National City Bank, 55 Wall Street (Box III.39, Folder 2)
  - National City Bank (Box III.39, Folder 3)
  - National City Bank (Box III.39, Folder 4)
  - National City Bank (Box III.39, Folder 5)
  - National City Company, 42nd Street and Madison Avenue, NY (Box III.40, Folder 1)
  - New York Institute for the Blind (Box III.40, Folder 2)
  - New York Institute for the Blind (Box III.40, Folder 3)
  - New York Institute for the Blind (Box III.40, Folder 4)
  - New York Institute for the Blind (Box III.40, Folder 5)
  - New York Institute for the Blind (Box III.40, Folder 6)
  - New York Institute for the Blind, Tool/Garden Shed (Box III.40, Folder 7)
  - New York Institute for the Blind, Pelham Parkway (Box III.40, Folder 8)
  - New York Institute for the Blind, Lower Level (Box III.41, Folder 1)
  - New York Post Graduate Hospital (Box III.41, Folder 2)
  - New York Post Office, Annex (Box III.42, Folder 1)
  - New York Post Office, Annex (Box III.42, Folder 2)
  - New York Post Office, Annex (Box III.42, Folder 3)
  - New York Post Office (Box III.42, Folder 4)
  - New York Post Office (Box III.43, Folder 1)
  - New York Post Office (Box III.43, Folder 2)
  - New York Post Office (Box III.43, Folder 3)
  - New York Post Office (Box III.43, Folder 4)
  - New York State Bar Association (Box III.44, Folder 1)
  - Northwestern Technological Institute, Northwestern University, Evanston, ILL (Box III.44, Folder 2)
  - Northwestern Technological Institute, Northwestern University, Evanston, ILL (Box III.44, Folder 3)
  - New York University (Box III.44, Folder 4)
  - New York University (Box III.45, Folder 1)
  - New York University (Box III.45, Folder 2)
  - New York World Fair 1930-1940, Business Code (Box III.45, Folder 3)
  - Palmer, Mrs. Potter., Mausoleum, Graceland Cemetery, Cook County, ILL (Box III.46, Folder 1)
  - Payne Whitney Esquire (Box III.46, Folder 2)
  - Peabody Administration Building, Nashville, TN (Box III.46, Folder 3)
  - Peabody Fine Art Building, Peabody College, Nashville, TN (Box III.46, Folder 4)
  - Peabody, George., Demonstration School, Nashville, TN (Box III.46, Folder 5)
  - Peddie School, Austin Colgate Hall, NJ (Box III.46, Folder 6)
  - Pennsylvania Station, Cooking apparatus and equipment (Box III.46, Folder 7)
  - Pennsylvania Station, Electrical Fixtures (Box III.46, Folder 8)
  - Pennsylvania Station, Floor Work (Box III.46, Folder 9)
  - Pennsylvania Station, Escalators (Box III.47, Folder 1)
  - Pennsylvania Station, General Construction (Box III.47, Folder 2)
  - Pennsylvania Station, General Construction (Box III.47, Folder 3)
  - Pennsylvania Station, Granite Work (Box III.47, Folder 4)
  - Pennsylvania Station and Boiler House, Harrison and Newark, NJ (Box III.47, Folder 5)
  - Pennsylvania Station and Boiler House, Harrison and Newark, NJ (Box III.47, Folder 6)
  - Pennsylvania Station and Boiler House, Harrison and Newark, NJ (Box III.48, Folder 1)
  - Pennsylvania Station, Interior Stone (Box III.48, Folder 2)
  - Pennsylvania Station, Iron Work (Box III.48, Folder 3)
  - Pennsylvania Station, Marble Work (Box III.48, Folder 4)
  - Pennsylvania Station, Newark, NJ (Box III.48, Folder 5)
  - Pennsylvania Station, Newark, NJ (Box III.49, Folder 1)
  - Pennsylvania Station, Newark, NJ (Box III.49, Folder 2)
  - Pennsylvania Station, Offices and Stores (Box III.49, Folder 3)
  - Pennsylvania Station, Plumbing (Box III.49, Folder 4)
  - Pennsylvania Railroad Station, Pittsburg, PA (Box III.50, Folder 1)
  - Pennsylvania Station, Steelwork (Box III.50, Folder 2)
  - Pennsylvania Station, Limestone and Tile Work (Box III.50, Folder 3)
  - Pennsylvania Station, Waterproofing and Fireproofing (Box III.50, Folder 4)
  - Pennsylvania Station, Woodwork (Box III.50, Folder 5)
  - Phillips D.C., Washington D.C. (Box III.50, Folder 6)
  - Porchester Library, Porchester NY (Box III.50, Folder 7)
  - Public School #4, Brooklyn, NY (Box III.50, Folder 8)
  - Public School #4, Brooklyn, NY (Box III.51, Folder 1)
  - Public School #4, Brooklyn, NY (Box III.51, Folder 2)
  - Plymouth Rock and Pilgrim Hall (Box III.51, Folder 3)
  - Radcliffe College (Box III.51, Folder 4)
  - Racquet and Tennis Club, Park Avenue, NY (Box III.51, Folder 5)
  - Racquet and Tennis Club, Park Avenue, NY (Box III.52, Folder 1)
  - Racquet and Tennis Club, Park Avenue, NY (Box III.52, Folder 2)
  - Redmond Johnston, Trivoli, NY (Box III.52, Folder 3)
  - Redmond Johnston, Trivoli, NY (Box III.52, Folder 4)
  - Rhode Island, State House (Box III.52, Folder 5)
  - Rochester Savings Bank (Box III.52, Folder 6)
  - Rumsey (Box III.52, Folder 7)
  - Saint Augustus Gardens- Memorial (Box III.53, Folder 1)
  - Saint Peter's Church, Morristown (Box III.53, Folder 2)
  - Savoy Plaza Hotel, NY (Box III.53, Folder 3)
  - Savoy Plaza Hotel, NY (Box III.53, Folder 4)
  - Schenectady City Hall, NY (Box III.54, Folder 1)
  - Schenectady City Hall, NY (Box III.54, Folder 2)
  - Seabreeze Hospital, Rockaway Point, NY (Box III.54, Folder 3)
  - Skinner, Mr. Joseph A., Monument (Box III.54, Folder 4)
  - Stapleton House, Sir Ronald C. Lindsay (Box III.54, Folder 5)
  - Sterling, John W. Esquire, Mausoleum (Box III.54, Folder 6)
  - Taylor, H.A.C. (Box III.54, Folder 7)
  - Tennessee War Memorial, Nashville, TN (Box III.55, Folder 1)
  - Tiffany Building Addition, 391 5th Avenue, NY (Box III.55, Folder 2)
  - Tiffany and Company Building, NY (Box III.55, Folder 3)
  - Tiffany and Company Garage (Box III.55, Folder 4)
  - The League for Political Education (Box III.55, Folder 5)
  - The Pacific Mills, 261 5th Avenue, NY (Box III.56, Folder 1)
  - "The Oaks" at Washington D.C. (Box III.56, Folder 2)
  - Triborough Bridge and Tunnel Authority, NY (Box III.56, Folder 3)
  - Trinity College, Chemistry Building, CT (Box III.56, Folder 4)
  - Trinity College, Chemistry Building, CT (Box III.56, Folder 5)
  - Trinity College, Cook Dormitories, CT (Box III.56, Folder 6)
  - Trinity College, Cook Dormitories, CT (Box III.56, Folder 7)
  - Trinity College, Field House, CT (Box III.57, Folder 1)
  - Trinity College, Field House, CT (Box III.57, Folder 2)
  - Trinity College, Field House, CT (Box III.57, Folder 3)
  - Tufts College, Dormitories, Posner Hall, Boston, MA (Box III.57, Folder 4)
  - Tufts College, Dormitories, Posner Hall, Boston, MA (Box III.57, Folder 5)
  - Twombly, H. Mck. Esquire Residence, Madison, NJ (Box III.57, Folder 6)
  - Twombly, H. Mck. Esquire Residence, Madison, NJ (Box III.58, Folder 1)
  - Twombly, H. Mck. Esquire Residence, Madison, NJ (Box III.58, Folder 2)
  - University Club, NY (Box III.58, Folder 3)
  - University Club, NY (Box III.59, Folder 1)
  - University Club, NY (Box III.59, Folder 2)
  - University Club, NY (Box III.59, Folder 3)
  - University of Connecticut, Dormitories (Box III.59, Folder 4)
  - University of Connecticut, Dormitories (Box III.60, Folder 1)
  - University of Connecticut, Dormitories (Box III.60, Folder 2)
  - University of Pennsylvania, Wharton School Building (Box III.60, Folder 3)
  - University of Rochester, Memorial Art Gallery, NY (Box III.60, Folder 4)
  - University of Vermont (Box III.60, Folder 5)
  - University of Vermont, Southwick Memorial (Box III.60, Folder 6)
  - University of Vermont, IRA Allen Chapel (Box III.61, Folder 1)
  - University of Vermont, Women's Dormitory (Box III.61, Folder 2)
  - Washington Heights, Educational Building, NY (Box III.61, Folder 3)
  - Wesleyan University, Biological Laboratory (Box III.61, Folder 4)
  - Wesleyan University, Downey House (Box III.61, Folder 5)
  - Wesleyan University, Gymnasium (Box III.61, Folder 6)
  - Wesleyan University, Hall Laboratory of Chemistry (Box III.61, Folder 7)
  - Wesleyan University, Harriman Hall (Box III.61, Folder 8)
  - Wesleyan University, Indoor Field (Box III.62, Folder 1)
  - Wesleyan University, Middletown, CT (Box III.62, Folder 2)
  - Wesleyan University, Olin Memorial Library (Box III.62, Folder 3)
  - Wesleyan University, Steps and Terraces (Box III.62, Folder 4)
  - Wesleyan University, Squash Court Building (Box III.62, Folder 5)
  - White House, Washington D.C. (Box III.62, Folder 6)
  - White, Stanford. Esquire Residence (Box III.62, Folder 7)
  - Whitney, W.C., Long Island (Box III.63, Folder 1)
  - Whitney W.C., City House, NY (Box III.63, Folder 2)
  - Willard, Joseph E., NY (Box III.63, Folder 3)
  - Willard, Joseph E., Richmond, VA (Box III.63, Folder 4)
  - Women's Golf and Tennis Club, Glen Head, LI (Box III.63, Folder 5)
  - 8th East 56th Street, NY (Box III.63, Folder 6)
- Series IV: Photographs
  - Subseries IV.1: Photographic prints
    This subseries is comprised of 68 boxes, primarily of photographs, but also including copy photos of architectural drawings, printed material (offprints from publications, entire publications, postcards), newspaper clippings, documents from Departments of Documents and Buildings (generally for New York City projects), handwritten notes, and sometimes correspondence or blueprints.
    Most of the photographs are site photographs, showing exteriors and interiors, made either prior to, during, or after construction (but generally undated). Photographers included are Blackman Photo Service, Edwin J. Cardswell, Louis H. Dreyer, Gottscho-Schleisner, H. Ernest King, Schuyler Carteret Lee, J.C. Maugans, C. Ording, Richard Averill Smith, Adolph Studly, Tebbs Architectural Photos, Irving Underhill, United States Army Signal Corps, DeWitt Ward, and Wurts Bros.
    The photographs are housed by size (small, medium and large), and within each size category are arranged alphabetically by project. A box and folder list is available on-site.
    - Sub-subseries IV.1.A: Small photographs
      Note
      Small photographs are arranged by project. A box and folder list is available on-site.
      - Projects A-Z (Box 1-42)
    - Sub-subseries IV.1.B: Medium photographs
      Medium photographs are arranged by project. A box and folder list is available on-site.
      - Projects A-Z (Box 43-65)
    - Sub-subseries IV.1.C: Large photographs
      - Unidentified interior (Box 66)
      - Harvard Club, exterior (Box 66)
      - Pennsylvania Station, photograph of a drawing (Box 66)
      - Pennsylvania Station, photograph of a plan (Box 66)